why does open aai need Microsoft to
build a hundred billion Stargate
supercomputer I'm going to try to give
you the answer to that question in this
video which in turn will give you
insight into the next 1 to four years of
AI development I'll also draw on a
discussion I had last night with the
perplexity founder and former openai
researcher aravan shrinivas about what
kind of breakthroughs this will lead to
and what AGI timelines he now has and no
this is not just about Sora and the open
aai voice engine this is about
manufacturing intelligence at hard to
imagine scales this report by the way
from the information came from three
different sources one of whom spoke to
Sam mman and another who viewed some of
Microsoft's initial cost estimates and
to give you some context if that data
center were a country then its cost as a
GDP would make it the 64th richest
country in the world this supercomputer
would likely be bed in the desert
somewhere in the US and would launch
around 2028 some other stages of The
Wider plan though will come online as
soon as this year and again before we
get to why they're doing this let me
give you a sense of the scale the
Stargate supercomputer would produce
orders of magnitude more computing power
than what Microsoft currently supplies
to open AI notice the plural orders of
magnitude an order of magnitude is a 10x
increase so orders of magnitude would be
at least a 100x increase and to give you
one little spoiler more computing power
more or less directly correlates to
increased capabilities for the frontier
AI models in even simpler terms 100
times more is a lot but why did that
sentence begin with an if if Stargate
moves forward well the previous
paragraph said this Microsoft's
willingness to go ahead with the
Stargate plan depends in part on open
ai's ability to meaningfully improve the
capabilities of its AI whether that
hinges on GPT 4.5 likely coming in the
spring or GPT 5 which many people are
now agreeing with me will come at the
end of this year or possibly the
beginning of next we don't know my
prediction by the way is that open AI
will meaningfully improve the
capabilities of its Ai and part of my
proof is in this video and therefore
Stargate will go ahead One Source said
that such a project is absolutely
required for artificial general
intelligence that's the kind of
intelligence that you would feel
comfortable hiring for most jobs and the
timelines for this data center dovea
tell quite nicely with my own prediction
for the first demonstration of an
artificial general intelligence system
now I know many of you will react to
that and say AGI is definitely coming
this year of course it depends on
definitions but let me give you a word
from aravan shrinivas the founder of the
newly minted unicorn perplexity that's
why you should always ask okay if you
are active really close to AGI if it is
the case that AGI is 5 years away why
are you hiring so many people right now
if you're really truly getting close to
AI why are you not you benefiting from
AGI yourself what like open AI is hiring
30 people or like 50 people a month or
100 people a month at that rate they're
going to hire like thousand a year and
over 5 years they would have had a
company with 5,000 10,000 employees so
why couldn't you do with 100 if AGI is
truly there how many people do you
really need anymore these are the kind
of questions you should ask and honestly
like someone has to physically go and
maintain the cluster make these
decisions on which gpus to use what
happens when these nodes fail like
systems crash and write all these heris
rules to deal with all these things if
something goes wrong in production code
like who has to go and work on the
backend servers can all these be done by
an AI now obviously not every time the
definition of AGI gets very narrow or
narrow and it feels like narrow Ai and
not AGI you see my point you should ask
D is when will he not have an executive
assistant and uh that maybe that day we
can call we have something like an AI
back to the article though and let me do
my first mini t i noticed a slight
mathematical discrepancy in that this
data center Stargate will produce orders
of magnitude as I said 100x more
computing power but in terms of actual
energy it will need the same amount of
Watts as what's needed to run several
large data centers today now of course
that's a lot but wouldn't you need even
more power than that to run something
that's going to give us 100x at least
more computing power well just for a few
seconds let me bring you this chart from
the chairman of tsmc that's the company
that makes around 90% of the world's
most advanced chips and one key number
comes at the top the energy efficient
performance improves 3x every 2 years so
straight from tsmc we get the projection
that in 4 years 2028 chips will be
almost 10 times more energy efficient I
thought that super interesting but in
case you're getting a little bit bored
where did the name Stargate come from
well the code name originated with open
AI named for the sci-fi film which
scientists develop a device for
traveling between galaxies and I
actually agree that the arrival of AGI
will be like Humanity stepping through a
portal can't go back and the world will
be changed forever but I know some of
you are thinking didn't Philip promise
to say why they're building Stargate not
just describe how they're building it so
let me get to the first reason they're
doing it to match Google samman has said
privately that Google one of open ai's
biggest Rivals will have more Computing
capacity than can open AI in the near
term and he's also complained publicly
about not having as many AI server chips
as he'd like this Insider chart from
semi analysis gives us a glimpse of the
scale of that discrepancy here we are
newly arriving into quarter 2 of 2024
and apparently the discrepancy is pretty
Stark between Google's capacity and open
AI in the words of Dylan Patel Google's
compute capabilities make everyone else
look silly indeed I remember around a
year year ago when I said that it's
likely Google who are on course to
create AGI first many people laughed and
said just look at Bard but I likened
Google and Google deep mine specifically
as like being a woken giant we have
started to Glimpse the power of Gemini
1.5 and Gemini 2 is likely coming in
June and if you didn't realize how
dependent open AI are on Microsoft to
compete with Google how about this the
CEO of Microsoft SAA Adella recently
posted that it would not matter if open
AI disappeared tomorrow we have all of
the intellectual property rights and all
of the capability we have the people we
have the compute and we have the data we
have everything we are below them above
them and around them it isn't only about
personnel and clever algorithms it's
about supercomputers it's about Stargate
okay so it's to match Google but what is
the next reason for building Stargate
well it would be to build models like
GPT 7 7.5 and 8 and yes I am well aware
that we don't even have GPT 4.5 so why
am I even talking about gpt7 well GPT 5
according to my own research which I
published in a video is likely training
around now in fact probably finished
around now of course that doesn't mean
we're going to get it around now they're
going to release smaller versions like
GPT 4.5 and they're going to do safety
testing but that's the full GPT 5 likely
coming at the end of this year or the
beginning of next that's trained on
current generation Hardware I would say
maybe 100,000 h 100s but this year and
next year the report says Microsoft has
planned to provide openai with servers
housing hundreds of thousands of gpus in
total and one former googler and
director y combinator leaked this he
spoke to a Microsoft engineer on the GPT
6 training cluster project that engineer
apparently complained about the pain
they were having essentially setting up
links between gpus in different regions
and naturally he asked why not just
locate the cluster in one region and the
Microsoft employee said oh yeah we tried
that first we can't put more than
100,000 h100s in a single state without
bringing down the power grid so clearly
it's going to be multiple 100,000 h100s
or b100s check out my previous video for
GPT 6 but then we have a smaller phase 4
supercomputer for open AI that aims to
launch around 2026 now of course the
naming schemes might go out the window
by this point but you can see why I
think that the Stargate supercomputer
for 2028 might be GPT 7.5 GPT 8 and it's
not like open AI aren't repeatedly
telling us that scale is the way to get
to AGI here's one of their star
researchers gome Brown saying recently
that he wished every AI startup founder
would read the bitter lesson now I might
do a video on that essay someday but
basically it says that it's not about
encoding human expert knowledge into the
model it's about building relatively
simple algorithms and then just just
scaling them up as much as you can it's
a bitter lesson because human expertise
and data become progressively less
relevant to the models performance just
like our bitter experience of seeing
Alpha go which was trained in part on
human expert performance in go being
superseded by Alpha zero which wasn't
likewise for human data on the path to
AGI here's Andre carpath until fairly
recently a star open AI researcher
speaking about a week ago cuz the
current modes are just like not good
enough and I think there are big rocks
to be turned here and I think people
still haven't like really seen what's
possible in the space uh like at all and
I like roughly speaking I think we've
done step one of alphago we've done
imitation learning part there's step two
of alphago which is the RL and people
haven't done that yet and I think it's
going to fundamentally like this is the
part that actually made it work and made
something super human but I think this
is we just haven't done step two of
alpago long story short and we've just
done imitation and I don't think that
people appreciate like number one like
how terrible the data collection is for
like JP say you have a problem like some
prompt is some kind of mathematical
problem a human comes in and gives the
ideal solution right to that problem the
problem is that the human psychology is
different from the model psychology
what's easy or hard for the mo for the
human are different to what's easy or
hard for the model and so human kind of
fills out some kind of a trace that like
comes to the solution but like some
parts of that are trivial to the model
and some parts of that are massive leap
that the model doesn't understand you're
kind of just like losing it and then
everything else is polluted by that
later and so like fundamentally what you
need is the model might the model needs
to practice itself uh how to solve these
problems it needs to figure out what
works for it or does not work for it but
it needs to learn that for itself based
on its own capability and its own
knowledge so that's number one is like
that's totally broken I think it's a
good initializer though for something
agent likee and then the other thing is
like we're doing reinforcement learning
from Human feedback but that's like a
super weak form of reinforcement
learning doesn't even count as
reinforcement learning I think so R CHF
is like nowhere near I would say RL is
like silly and the other thing is
imitation learning super silly rhf is
nice Improvement but it's still silly
and I think people need to look for
better ways of training these models so
that it's in the loop with itself and
its own psychology and I think we're uh
there will probably be unlocks in that
direction this Echoes again gome Brown
who I believe is working on open ai's
qar system who said you don't get
superhuman performance by doing better
imitation learning on human data and
that brings me nicely to the third
reason for building Stargate doing long
inference AKA letting the models think
for longer before they output a response
in the case of alphago allowing the
models to ponder or think for a minute
improve the systems by the equivalent of
scaling those systems by 100,000x or in
other words GPT 5 might be reminiscent
of GPT 6 if we let it think for a minute
let it think for hours and hours or even
days and we might get a new cancer drug
and before you immediately say he's just
getting silly now well check out this
article from The Economist AI is taking
over drug development of course there is
way more detail and Nuance than I can
get to in this video but the conclusion
was this generative Ai and systems like
Alpha fold are already significantly
accelerating biotechnology and we will
see in the next few years whether that
will bring us usable drugs the analyst
they say at Boston Consulting Group see
signs of a fast approaching AI enabled
wave of new drugs indeed drug Regulators
will need to up their game to meet the
challenge it would be a good problem for
the world to have of course I asked the
perplexity CEO about qar and his
predictions of the impacts of that
system this year but first a 30C plug
for AI insiders that's my patreon link
in the description where first of all
you get exclusive videos this one from a
few days ago I am particularly proud of
I analyzed a 44-page new report on the
so-called AI jobs apocalypse and within
36 hours I had interviewed the author
and produced this video trust me I
definitely dig beyond the headlines on
insiders you can also ask questions of
my forthcoming guests and I use many of
the questions from insiders when I
interviewed aravind our Discord I'm
proud to say also has a ton of
professional best practice sharing
across dozens of professions and Fields
just a few hours ago we got a new
expert-led Forum on semiconductors and
hardware and just a few days before that
a new Forum on alignment led by a goog
we also have Regional networking across
Europe and North America but here's
aravind on what he believes qar is and
how soon it's coming so if you just
clean up all the internet data and teach
these models to go through reasoning
chains before writing an answer they're
all they're going to get a lot more
reliable and uh then you can think of
models that can search over the Chain of
Thought before giving you an answer
rather than like decoding a single Chain
of Thought this whole tree of thought
concept and then you can and then you
can extend that to saying thinking of
models that will have like a search over
a tree and identify like several chains
and look at the most possible
explanation based on the probabilities
almost like how a player in a go or
chess match reasons through several
different branches of moves and like
picks the one that has the highest odds
of success at winning the game you can
think of inference time itself going up
right now you use the system chpt to
just respond in a few seconds water AIS
are are decoding with these really giant
models even bigger than gp4 going
through several reasons of chains of
reasoning several layers of depth in it
and comes back to you after an hour with
something that feels incredibly Inyo now
this could be called an AI like by some
people I'm sure Denis or Sam would call
this an AGI if it works because the
definition that they would use here is
something that truly surprises humans
marvelous things right like like feels
like alabo or something where it's not
something most humans would be able to
come up with it requires several horor
of thinking so maybe we'll go far along
those Dimensions might not replace our
executive Assistance or sales and
marketing or designers or like
programmers but might feel like a 10x
programmer might feel like a 10x
marketer and I think that could happen
and that could be a dimension where we
see AGI progress in the near term and I
see maybe some breakthrough like this
happening in 24 so far nothing but at
least by this time next year I think
something like that will be possible
you'll see a demo where it doesn't
respond immediately but it thinks for
quite a long time and gets back with a
really cool response and I can't help
but point out that if you watch my qar
video I said one of the stars of the new
system was Lucas Kaiser one of the
co-authors of the original Transformers
paper and I would note that in this
week's wired interview when he was asked
about qar the open AI PR person almost
leapt across the table to silence him I
definitely think I was on to something
and believe it or not there is actually
a fourth reason for a Stargate like
supercomputer dominating different
modalities whether that's audio video or
even embedded in robotics as we saw in
my last video but let's just take audio
and video we learned a few days ago that
open AI have had their voice engine
system since 2022 basically you can feed
it 15 seconds of someone's voice and it
can then imitate that voice with High
Fidelity now if you have lost your voice
due to illness this is simply incredible
and I've already demonstrated what 11
Labs can do before on this channel but
of course a system like this comes with
the risks this is how good the system
was at imitating your voice 2 years ago
here's the real person's voice force is
a push or pull that can make an object
move stop or change Direction imagine
you're riding a bike down a hill first
the push you give off the ground is the
force that gets you going and here is
the generated audio of that person
saying whatever you'd like in this case
let's take biology some of the most
amazing habitats on Earth are found in
the rainforest a rainforest is a place
with a lot of precipitation and it has
many kinds of animals trees and other
plants tropical rainforests are usually
not too far from the equator and are
warm all year and as gome brown has said
yes him again if you haven't disabled
voice authentication for your bank
account and had a conversation with your
family about AI voice impersonation yet
now would be a good time my only
question is what are banks going to use
not your voice and definitely not your
handwriting as I talked about back in in
January AI can mimic your handwriting
perfectly and not your face right
because we all know about deep fakes
well maybe a video of you but I think
almost all of us know about the progress
that's being made in photorealistic text
to video I'm going to show you an
extract from what I think is actually
quite a beautiful video prompted by an
artist but generated by Sora from open
aai I am literally filled with hot air
yeah living like this has its challenges
uh windy days for one are particularly
Troublesome or there was the one time my
girlfriend insisted I'd go to the cactus
store to get my Uncle Jerry a wedding
present what do I love most about my
predicament the perspective it gives me
you know I get to see the world
differently I float above the mundane
and the ordinary I see things a
different way from everyone else the
creators if that's the right word to use
of that clip were shy kids the company
not the children of course they said as
great as Sora is at generating things
that appear real what excites us is its
ability to make things that are totally
surreal and that's a tough one isn't it
cuz I think that clip really showcases
how you can be creative with AI I would
indeed call that art but I can easily
see the RIS to the economic value of
artist's work at the same time here's
how the term AI went down at one recent
artist conference and Festival look out
into this room you can tell that AI is a
culture artificial intelligence is it's
here should be an AI thinker you know
your business is going to be disrupted
and we need
[Applause]
to but let me know what you think not
only about ai's impact on Art but
whether you agree with me that we are in
a sense going through a Stargate we
don't know how the world will be
transformed by AGI and when it's created
and we've stepped through the portal
it's hard to see a way back I'd love to
know your thoughts and as ever thank you
so much for watching to the end and have
a wonderful day