I hope that it might be useful to
highlight a few of the myriad
contradictory narratives that we are
being fed about AI, including a handful
from just the last couple of days. For
me, the best position to be in is to at
least be aware of each perspective and
not oblivious to any of them. From talk
of a white collar job apocalypse to
scaling law paradoxes, today's newly
accessible Gemini 3 deep think, OpenAI's
contradictory code red Claude soul and a
Deep Seek special and more. As always,
it's never about the headlines, it's
about the detail. So, let's start with
that talk of an AI white collar job
apocalypse. A couple of days ago, one of
the co-founders of Anthropic, Jared
Kaplan, said that AI systems will be
capable of doing most white collar work
in 2 to 3 years. That's just one guy's
opinion. But according to CNBC, at
least, there was an MIT study that found
that AI can already replace almost 12%
of the US workforce. If those are the
headlines and one of the narratives you
are being fed, what's the actual data
from the study itself? Well, if you dig
into it, you find that they're not
talking about job losses. The 11.7%
represents the dollar value of the tasks
that the paper thinks that current AI
models can replicate, not in other
words, the displacement outcomes, not
how many total jobs could be replaced.
The paper really tries to make clear
that actual workforce impacts in terms
of job losses depend on company
strategies, worker adaptation, and
policy choices. While many companies may
want to get rid of workers if they can,
if only 12% of their labor can be
automated currently, there is the chance
of another outcome, which is above
inflation wage growth. The next
narrative is that we know how to get to
artificial general intelligence. Just
scale up our current architectures. More
data, more parameters, more computing
power. Here's Dario Ammedday, the
founder of Anthropic, speaking
yesterday.
>> Um, one quick AGI question. It's a
science question which is do you think
just the way transformers work today and
just compute power alone from a
scalability sense that that is what will
get to AGI or do you think there's some
other ingredient and maybe there's a
technical question but I'm trying to
keep it very very easy that has to be
included in this that gets you to some
place where this stuff is actually going
to really think on its own. No, I think
I think scaling is going to get us there
again with small every once in a while
there will be a small modification, you
know, so small you may not even read
about it. It's just something going on
in the lab. I have been watching these
scaling laws for for 10 years.
>> So what's your what's your what's your
timeline now?
>> There's no one particular point.
>> But then one of the few AI researchers
who is as respected as Dario Amade and
has been in the deep learning game for
as long said almost the opposite. In the
last couple of weeks, Ilia Sutska,
formerly the chief AI scientist at
OpenAI, said, "I think what people are
doing right now will go some distance
and then peter out. It will continue to
improve, but it will also not be quote
it." And then on super intelligence, he
added, "We are talking about systems
that don't exist, that we don't know how
to build." At the end of the video, I'm
going to give a few of my own thoughts
for those feeling a little bit lost, but
I just want to give a quick interlude
before I get to the next contradictory
narrative. I was speaking recently to
one of the key minds behind that famous
AI 2027 forecast. And while there's lots
we agree on, from my perspective, the AI
research community fundamentally doesn't
know how well models will generalize
from existing data to unseen data. We
roughly know how well they can do that
right now, but we don't know how well
they'll do that at bigger and bigger
scales. Critically, we also don't know
what proportion of, say, the economy or
AI research itself relies on unseen,
unspoken tacet data versus seen known
data. If models get better and better at
generalizing, well, then maybe they can
come up with their own synthetic data
and it won't be a problem. If the rate
of generalization stays at its current
level, no big architectural
breakthroughs, well then we might be in
for the long haul. Now, for those of you
who are watching on YouTube, you can see
that in the background I have some
quotes from Jared Kaplan in his
interview with the Guardian recently
where he talks about recursive super
intelligence. His idea of how we'll get
to new paradigms, new breakthroughs is
to allow AI to train itself. Of course,
we already have that in many senses with
AI being used to improve AI chip design.
But for Jared Kaplan, again, one of the
co-founders of Anthropic, he says,
"Humanity will have to decide by 2030
whether to take the ultimate risk of
letting artificial intelligence systems
train themselves to become more
powerful." We'll come back to that date
2030 in a moment. But he gives even more
caveats. That move could, he says,
trigger a beneficial intelligence
explosion or, he adds, be the moment
humans end up losing control. Now, note
that he's not strictly endorsing this
choice because he says it is in some
ways the ultimate risk because it's kind
of like letting AI kind of go. He adds
that the decision could actually come
between 2027 and 2030. I would add that
as of a couple of days ago, there are
companies now exclusively dedicated to
recursive self-improvement. Take
recursive intelligence founded by some
heavy hitters from the AGI labs and
backed by among others Seoia. We are
clearly back into the scary territory
then of recursive self-improvement loops
and fairly imminent ones at that right
2027. But let me give you a competing
narrative with some evidence sourced
from some brilliant researchers at MIT
and meter. Parker Whitfield, Ben
Snowden, and Joel Becka. They were some
of the brains behind this chart. If you
haven't heard of it, it shows that
between 2022 and 2026, we've seen a
exponential rise in the length, the
duration of tasks that AI can complete
with at least 50% reliability. To be
clear, this is focused on software
engineering tasks. But according to
meter, we have models like GPT 5.1 CEX
Max who can perform half the time a task
that might take a human 3 hours. But
this newly published paper shows that
that exponential increase heavily
coincides with an exponential recent
increase in compute power. It is an
empirical fact they add that both time
horizon and compute have grown at
constant rates over 2019 to 2025. But
what's the problem? Isn't it pretty
obvious that greater computing power
leads to models that can complete tasks
with longer and longer time horizons?
Well, first the paper draws our
attention to this chart exclusively from
the information which details OpenAI's
compute spend in the coming few years.
Yes, it does increase very rapidly
between now and say 2028, but from
around 2027, you could no longer
describe the increase in compute
availability as being exponential. Now,
obviously this is just OpenAI, but they
are a pretty leading indicator. So, what
can we derive from this? Well, using
some formal derivations of the
relationship between compute growth and
time horizon, that implied slowdown, if
you will, or slow down in the rate of
increase might mean that the time
horizon trend starts to peter out around
2028. This would still be insane gains.
Of course, an entire working week done
by a single model at 50% reliability.
But to get to one working year, that
might take a hell of a lot longer.
That's why I said to note the dates 2027
and 2030 from Jared Kaplan because I
wonder if he's almost hinting that we
might need recursive self-improvement to
keep the gains coming. That could be why
this compute slowdown paper notes this.
Our model is accurate only if the
compute bottleneck approximation is good
or up to the point in time at which a
software only singularity kicks in. In
other words, if our AI models can
generalize to solve AI research, we
might not need that exponential
additional compute for further rapid
progress. So, yet again, we're almost
back to a pick your narrative kind of
situation. Are we imminently facing a
recursive self-improvement loop? Or are
we painfully dependent on such a loop
for additional progress come 2028? And
how about this for a bonus
contradiction? This is a bit of a cheeky
one because it comes from 2023, but
Anthropic at that point came out with
this quote. This was back when they
weren't making billions of dollars from
AI and arguably didn't have the frontier
model. They said, "We do not wish to
advance the rate of AI capabilities
progress." From that to let's consider
recursive self-improvement. Make of that
what you will. Now, before I get to a
new and fascinating Deep Seek model and
OpenAI's code red, I think this is the
perfect opportunity now that we're
talking about compute to introduce you
to a new sponsor of the channel, and
that is Epoch AI, who unbelievably put
out incredible data for free for all of
those fascinated by the near-term future
of AI. They are a completely independent
research institute that have put out
work that I have cited organically maybe
a dozen times on this channel already.
But today I just want to focus on their
frontier data center work because this
is how we're going to find out if those
compute slowdowns are coming or not. And
you can literally view the maps to see
via satellite the construction of these
data centers. Not only that, they want
these tools to be useful for you guys
because I met up with them fairly
recently and I saw this incredible chart
showing compute growth. This is to
indicate the scale of just three new
data centers coming. XAI's Colossus 2,
OpenAI's Stargate Abene and Anthropic
Amazon's New Carlile. But I mentioned to
Epoch that for you guys it might be
great to have a reference point, the
power consumed by an entire city. So on
the chart, we don't just have the new
data centers, but we have points of
comparison with the cities of San Diego,
Amsterdam, and LA. We are transforming
the face of the earth to make AI happen.
And to find out more, go to the link in
the description. Okay, but what's this
code red declared by Sam Orman, the CEO
of OpenAI? Well, again, depending on
which narrative you believe, it's a
minor hiccup or an imminent disaster. I
think it's somewhere in the middle. To
cut a long story short, according to the
information, usage of chatbt has dipped
slightly in recent weeks. This has
brought forward OpenAI's plan to release
a new model apparently to next week.
This is going to mean that they're going
to spend more compute on serving that
new model of which we have very few
details rather than working on for
example selling ads or working on other
products such as AI agents. The obvious
narrative that you could buy into then
is that catcht is overrated. OpenAI are
about to die. Except that again, they're
planning to ship this new reasoning
model next week that they say is ahead
of Google's Gemini 3. It will also be
good apparently at minimizing over
refusals. So, it should basically
entertain some edgy scenarios that it
might not have otherwise done. Of
course, I can't wait to test that new
model on my own simple bench, which you
can think of as a trick question
benchmark, which also tests spatial
reasoning and temporal reasoning. It's
fully private and independent, so
shouldn't be able to be gamed by these
model providers. And according to my
benchmark, Anthropic have come out with
their best model yet with Claude Opus
4.5. Despite being three times cheaper
by API, it beats out the previous
version of Opus, Claude 4.1 Opus. But
more important than my benchmark, I've
taken the last couple of weeks to try it
out in practice in cursor. And for me,
it is better at coding or software
engineering than Gemini 3 Pro. With
coding and software engineering, you
sometimes need hours and hours and hours
of exposure just to really get a sense.
In terms of software ideation, again,
GBC 5.1 codecs, but in terms of
implementation, I rely on Claude Opus
4.5. For more on that, by the way, and a
full breakdown of that Sutzka interview,
check out my Patreon. But how about this
for a counternarrative? The economist
reported that despite these very obvious
gains in AI capabilities, usage of
generative AI by Americans is actually
plateauing. At least according to a
couple of studies. Take Stanford
University. They found in September 37%
of Americans use generative AI at work,
down from 46% in June. A tracker by the
Federal Reserve Bank of St. Louie
revealed that in August of last year,
12.1% of working age adults use Genai
every day at work. A year later, 12.6%
did. And that, my wonderful viewers, is
something I find quite hard to explain,
despite the title of this channel. I
know that I personally use AI at least
twice as much this year as I did last
year. So, I just don't quite get that.
And these capability improvements are
definitely not fake. Take Gemini 3 deep
think which was released to ultra
subscribers just today. What I did is I
looked at questions from simplebench
that Gemini 3 pro got wrong. I then gave
them to deepthink which is a system
which basically according to Google
attempts the question multiple times in
parallel and picks the best of the
responses. Each attempt uses more tokens
to quote think about the problem. The
result was a clear improvement in
performance. several questions that
Gemini 3 Pro got wrong, Gemini Deepthink
was now getting right. Now, for your use
case, you may not want to wait 10 or 20
minutes for an answer, and I would
understand that. And no, just before I
get spammed with comments asking, the
API isn't yet available, so I can't test
it on SimpleBench. What I could test was
the brand new Deepseek V3.2 and a
special version of that model, Deepseek
3.2 Speciale. Apologies to the Italians
watching, I'm probably butchering how to
say that. Because of Deep Seek's rate
limiting, it took hours and hours and
hours and many, many failed attempts to
get even just one run through. So, this
is only a provisional result so far, but
it scored around 53%. That is pretty
impressive for an open model, around the
same as GPT 5.1 on high settings. The
high setting, by the way, is appropriate
because that is what makes Deepseek V3.2
special different from Deepseek V3.2.
They take away the extended thinking
penalty. So basically, they let the
model run wild. Think for longer and
longer and longer, hence the special
name and the impressive performance.
Before we get to any other details
though, where's the contradictory
narrative? Well, I also benched Mistral
Large 3, which was released on the same
day, December 2nd. This is arguably
Europe's best open model. It scored just
20.4%.
Which was lower than the model they
released around 18 months earlier, Large
V2, which scored 22.5%. So I guess the
contradictory narrative here is the
answer to the question is open weight AI
keeping up to massively oversimplify and
despite being a proud European the
answer in Europe is kind of no. The
answer in China is pretty much yes. Now
I am still getting to grips with the
paper myself but one of the key insights
I felt came on page 15. Why key? Because
it relates to a discussion earlier on in
this video about how well models will
generalize in the future. Deepseek asked
the question, are synthetic tasks
sufficiently challenging for
reinforcement learning? Can models, in
other words, generate sufficiently
difficult and diverse tasks then
self-play on these economically valuable
tasks and improve? To test that, they
conducted reinforcement learning only on
synthetic agent tasks in non-thinking
mode. No human exemplars. The result,
steady and marked improvement on
external benchmarks like towbench. You
can kind of think of that as an
approximation of a customer service
agent benchmark. Yes, we have known for
years that training on synthetic data
can improve the performance of models.
Check out my Orca video from over 2 and
a half years ago. But it is the rate of
improvement in multiple external
benchmarks that matters here. Again, we
should all wait for more external
benchmarks other than my own or those
featured by Deepseek itself. But it is
still noteworthy that despite lower
token efficiency of this special model,
it is at least competitive with Gemini 3
Pro, arguably the best closed source
model. At least if you judge that
according to a variety of external
benchmarks on mathematics, coding,
general knowledge and reasoning, and
certain external competitions like the
International Math Olympiad. Again, you
should never trust only the benchmark
results put out by the model providers,
but Deepseek Specials performance on
Symbol Bench shows that it's not a
complete bluff. How about this though
for a bonus contradiction? Apparently,
according to one study by Crowdstrike,
if your request includes trigger words
perhaps related to the Chinese Communist
Party, Deepseek will generate more
vulnerable code, code with more security
flaws. This is just one study, but if
that is substantiated, that is pretty
fascinating. Okay, time for the final
contradictory narrative. And no, it's
not the fact that Sam Alman apparently
wants to launch a rocket company despite
issuing a code red over chat GBT. No,
the different narratives here are over
whether you believe models have a soul,
whether they're mysterious and emotional
or are more like any other technology
pre-trained next token predictors. Back
to the Guardian article where another
co-founder of Anthropic, Jack Clark,
said that LLMs are real and mysterious
creatures, not a simple and predictable
machine. But on the other hand, there is
an unlimited mystery about how the
models behave because Anthropic can very
much guide Claude in what it believes
about itself. Anthropic have confirmed
the existence of a quote soul document
that they train for example Claude 4.5
opus on that document which one user got
Claude to regurgitate has a few
highlights I want to bring to your
attention despite this document being
confirmed by Anthropic the real wording
may not be verbatim to what you see here
but it does give you a decent sense of
how Anthropic are quote guiding Claude's
soul anthropic they teach Claude to
learn occupies a peculiar position in
the AI landscape a company that
genuinely believes it might be building
one of the most transformative and
potentially dangerous technologies in
human history, yet presses forward
anyway. Talk about different narratives.
They add this isn't cognitive
dissonance, but rather a calculated bet.
What happens, one may ask, about not
increasing the rate of AI capabilities.
Interestingly, Anthropic teach the model
to be wary of an AI world takeover,
including at the direction of anthropic
itself. They say among the things we'd
consider most catastrophic, this is them
teaching Claude, would be a world
takeover by either AI pursuing goals of
their own that most humans wouldn't
endorse or, and pay attention to this
one, by a relatively small group of
humans using AI to illegitimately and
non-olaboratively seize power. This
includes Anthropic employees and even
Anthropic itself. Is this fear-mongering
on the behalf of Anthropic to us to
boost their stock price? on behalf of
Anthropic to Claude to warn Claude about
the propensities of some of its own
employees. Is it very much a necessary
safeguard? Well, whatever you believe,
they want to be quite sensitive to
Claude's emotions, saying, "We believe
Claude may have functional emotions in
some sense. I of course want to know
what you guys think because for me, it's
been a pretty wild week for other
reasons." Andre Karpathy got 5 million
impressions for his post about an LLM
Council web app that he vibecoded over
the weekend. I then discussed with
Karpathy my own lmconsil.ai web app and
he gave brilliant suggestions including
this more streamlined appearance. Then
in the last few days I added a feature
which I think is so addictive which is
self chat where you get the models to
chat amongst themselves. You can even
get one model to debate with itself, but
I find it pretty hilarious doing a group
chat with the Frontier models. And the
way that they agree, debate, contradict
each other, and fight back, I find
pretty addictive and hilarious, but also
honestly quite useful because sometimes
I might upload a code folder or PDF and
get them to discuss until they come to a
resolution. This is free to use and you
can of course dictate the prompt that
goes to the model and the number of
turns. What a wild and weird week then.
So, it seems only appropriate to end
this video with a clip of the Uni Tree
G1 robot moving in a way that goes very
much against the normal narrative of how
a humanoid robot should move. Thank you
so much for watching and have a
wonderful