One of the easiest ways to make videos
stand out is to use visual effects. If
you watch my Friday news videos, they
always start with some sort of like
random visual effect, and it's probably
the thing that I get the absolute most
questions and comments about. Not to
mention, they're just super fun to make.
Now, before I get into this, I don't
like to make full-on AI generated
videos. I still like humans to create
stuff. So, here's a bunch of cool
effects that you can make with AI tools.
And all of these tools are actually
publicly available right now. Some of
the effects you can do in different
tools and we'll get different results
with different tools. But let's just get
into it and start playing around with
some of them. Let's start with some of
those intros that you see in my videos.
You know, stuff like THIS
and stuff like this.
I've done a ton of intros that follow
that same formula and most of them are
done inside of Runway. You can just see
I've done a lot of them now, but I
actually start in Da Vinci Resolve. So,
if I open up Da Vinci Resolve here, I
actually start by recording my video
like off of my seat. So, here's an
example that I'll pull in from my most
recent news video. And you'll notice in
the very beginning of the video, I'm not
on camera. I actually hit record by sort
of like reaching in, pressing the button
while I'm not on screen so that I have a
frame of what my room looks like without
me sitting in it yet. If I scrub forward
a little bit, you'll see I sit down,
position myself, and then start talking.
So, I need two still frames from this
video to get the effect. So, I'll go
back to the beginning before I'm on
camera, select my timeline, come up to
file, export in Da Vinci Resolve, and
then take current frame as still. I'll
usually save this as like frame one. And
then I come to right before I start
talking. So let me zoom in even more on
my timeline to right before I start
talking here. So the transition feels
more seamless right into me talking. And
I will export another frame here. So
file export current frame is still and
then frame two. Once I have those two
frames, I then jump into runway, click
on custom on the left side, and then
select key frame. And then it gives you
the option to upload the first video
frame and the last video frame. So for
our first video frame, we're going to
upload frame one. And for our last video
frame, we'll upload frame two. So you
could see me without the chair, me in
the chair. I'll then give it a simple
prompt like the man burst through the
back wall and then sits down in the
chair. I like to use seed dance 2.0, but
there are other models you can use here.
The cling model is actually pretty good
and Google's VO3.1 model is also pretty
good for this kind of thing. But seed
dance honestly like really kind of tops
them all right now. So I'll use Seed
Dance 2.0. And then you could decide
whether or not you wanted to output with
audio on or off. I always output with
audio on cuz if I don't like the audio,
I could just mute it inside of Da Vinci
Resolve. Also, you can use Seed Dance
and most of these models in like almost
any video generator. So if you're using
Runway, you can do it. I believe Crea
has all of these. I believe Higsfield
has all of these. I believe Leonardo has
most of these. I just mostly use Runway
because at some point like a year and a
half ago, Runway gave me a ton of
credits to play around with this tool
and I still have a lot of those credits.
So that's the main reason I use Runway.
But feel free to use whatever tool has
these models in it. We'll click generate
and when it's done, I get a video that
looks like this.
Now, typically I would re-roll it and
have it do it again so it doesn't do
this little like hard cut from zoomed in
on me to zoomed out. But just for demo
purposes, I'll show you the next step
here. I'll go ahead and download this.
Jump back into Da Vinci Resolve. I'll
cut out everything before I start
talking here. Drag this in and it should
be pretty close. The colors change a
little bit, but it's not too bad. And
then in Da Vinci, they have a effect.
So, if I open up my effects box and then
go to video transitions. They have one
called smooth cut which kind of cleans
up the transition a little bit so it's
less noticeable. So, I'll zoom in here.
I'll take a couple frames off of this
side. Take a couple frames off of this
side here. And then I'll use this smooth
cut transition. And you'll notice that
here's the it kind of tries to blend it
a little bit better so the transition's
less noticeable. And that's how I do
most of those intros. There's a few
variations that I've tried. Like for
example, I did this one where a claw
machine comes and picks me up here. It
lifts me up and then sets me in my chair
and then I start talking. The only
difference between the other one is I
didn't start off frame. I hit record,
walked over, sat in the corner of my
room, got up, moved to my chair, and
then just spliced out everything in
between. So frame one is just me sitting
in my corner. And then the final frame
is me sitting at my chair about to talk.
And here's the exact prompt I used. If
you want, feel free to pause and read
the exact prompt. Now, another variation
was this sort of like anamorph one that
I was trying to do, and this is
something I still find all of these AI
models are really bad at, is starting
from an animal and having it like morph
into a human. You can actually see as I
scrub through these, none of them are
that great at morphing from animal to
human. I think that might have been the
one I ended up using right here.
I like this one here where my head's
there first [laughter] and then my body
grows out of it. I did eventually find
one that I think worked decently well.
And for this one, what I did was I
actually started the way I would
normally start, me not in a chair at
all. Walk in, sit down, and then I still
exported the first frame without me in
it and also the frame right before I
start speaking. I then went over to chat
GPT, uploaded the image of me not in my
chair yet, and just said, "Make a wolf
sitting in the chair. Make sure to keep
the same 16x9 aspect ratio and it gave
me this image. And then I used this
image as my starting frame. So you could
see wolf as the starting frame, me as
the finishing frame, and then here was
my prompt right here if you want to
pause and look at the exact prompt. But
that's pretty much how I'm making all of
those intros. Here's another thing I
love to do if I know I'm going to be
shooting in a different location is I
like to do transitions to the new
location. So, for example, a news video
I did a couple weeks ago started like
this. In fact, for this one, let's
change up the scenery a little bit.
So, there wasn't a ton of AI news. So,
for this one, I knew I was going to be
up in Big Bear at a cabin recording. So,
before I left for Big Bear, I actually
recorded the first, you know, 5 seconds
of this in my office saying, "Here's the
AI news. Let's have a change of
scenery." So, it was just a little bit
of foresight knowing that I was going to
be recording in another location. You
can see here's my frames. The very last
shot from me at my house and then the
very first frame of me talking out in
Big Bear. And I just said the camera
rotates above the head of the man on the
first frame and then rotates around him
to reveal the second image. It does it
all in one smooth motion and the man
does not speak. And I put and the man
does not speak at the end because
oftentimes these models will do the
transition and then just make me speak
like gibberish at the end. So I need to
often prompt it like make sure the
person doesn't speak. And this was the
output of that. It took it and it just
transferred between the two scenes. You
can see it's actually a different
microphone. I'm holding this microphone
here and in this one I'm holding this
style microphone. And it happened so
quick you barely even noticed that the
microphone changed. But I also knew to
wear the same shirt. So, I was wearing
the same shirt before I left in my
studio. And when I was recording out in
the cabin, I made sure to wear that
exact same shirt when I was recording
just to kind of sell the transition.
When I found out I was speaking at NAB,
they asked me to make some video samples
of some of the cool like animations I've
done and transitions. And I made one and
it never ended up getting shown. So,
here's actually that video that I was
going to show at NAB that I'm actually
showing for the first time anywhere. I'm
currently in San Diego and I need to be
out in Vegas pretty quickly here. So,
uh, I've got a trick. All I got to do is
this
>> and I'm here. That was easy.
>> So, it's always fun to make little
transitions like that when you're going
from one place to the other. That one
was done in exactly the same way I just
showed you with this one. The only real
difference with this one is that I used
the cling video model instead of Seed
Dance and I did it inside of Leonardo
instead of Runway cuz I had credits over
there when I made that one. But the
process exactly the same. And here's
another variation of that same effect.
Toss the mic in the air. It sort of slow
motion spins and then falls into my hand
in the new location. And here's an
example of me getting sucked through a
wormhole and spit out the other side.
Here's
another one.
So, yeah, transitions are a lot of fun
[laughter] with AI. It's also fun to
make things happen in your video that
didn't really happen in real life. Like,
the majority of the video is something
that really happened, but something else
going around you didn't happen. For
example, I did this intro in one of my
videos where I'm talking and a yeti
walks by in the background and I don't
acknowledge it or even talk about it at
all. It just kind of happens. For these
kinds of effects, the best tool right
now is probably Google's Omni. So to do
this, I would record the first, you
know, 10 seconds of me talking in my
video here, and then take that 10-second
clip of me talking in the video, upload
that video here into Google's Gemini,
and put a prompt like a yeti walks by in
the background behind the man, and then
you get a clip like this where I'm
talking in the foreground, and the yeti
just walks by in the background. And I
splice it into the front of my video
just like I do any other video. This was
something else I was playing around with
in a video from like last week sometime
where I had this clip from Google IO of
this band playing
and I thought it would be fun to have
Godzilla come in and stomp around in
this scene. So I took this video clip,
tossed it into Gemini and said make
Godzilla enter the scene and start
stomping around. And this was the output
from that one.
>> [music]
>> You can also add little effects to the
back of your video. Like for example, I
took one of the intros to one of my
videos here and I said, "Add an
explosion behind me in the video. Don't
change anything else. Make it so I don't
even react or notice that happened."
Now, I have to add that extra bit to the
prompt cuz otherwise like I'd turn
around and go and act like I noticed it
happened. And I want in this particular
case to just be like nothing's going on.
So for this one, here's an explosion in
the background.
Here's the AI news. you probably missed
this week. So, for this one, I took that
same exact video clip and said, "Make my
head smoking." And so, this one, I do my
normal intro and there's just smoke
coming off of my head. And then here's
another one that started as a clip from
Google IO where everybody's just sort of
walking in. It's clearly a bright, sunny
day. Everything looks nice. The
weather's amazing. And I said, "Take
that same video, but make it a cloudy
and rainy day." But now you can see it's
the same location, but it's a cloudy,
rainy day and everybody's wearing
jackets and holding umbrellas and it
totally changed the environment, but the
location's exactly the same. Now, let's
talk about generating B-roll for your
videos cuz this is something that
anybody who makes videos knows they need
from time to time, and sometimes you
can't find the exact footage you need on
stock video sites. For example, a
channel like mine where I share news and
articles and curate things, I like to be
able to highlight things on a web page
and make it look nice. For that, I
actually use a surprising tool that gets
the job done, and that's Claude Co-work.
So, check this out. This is my Claude
account here, my Claude Co-work app. And
for this, I'm using Opus 4.8. Now, you
can use Fable for this. And Fable will
probably do a little bit better of a job
than Opus, but Opus honestly does the
trick. Now, if you scroll all the way
up, you can see what my prompt here is.
Create a video for me. The video starts
with a screenshot of this page. I linked
it up to this news article about Claude
co-work is coming to mobile and web and
I want it to zoom down to a paragraph
down here that says your work follows
you. You start a task at your desk.
Check out from your phone. Pick up the
finished output anywhere. I want an
animation that starts on this article,
scrolls down to that text, and then
highlights the text for me. So I said,
"Create the video for me." The video
starts with a screenshot of this page.
It scrolls down to the text that says,
"Your work follows you, etc., etc. It
zooms in on the page slightly and then
uses a highlighter animation to
highlight the text. And then what it
does is it actually goes and it
screenshots that website. And you can
see it wrote a bunch of code for me and
did a bunch of tasks and used a bunch of
tools. And once it was all done, it
literally spit out an MP4 video for me.
So if I click download and open here, we
can see this is the video that it
created. There's a little bit of a
wonkiness in the image here, but it's
not horrible. But you can see I press
play and it scrolls down the video for
me, zooms in on that section and then
highlights it and that's the whole
video. But that's usable B-roll if I'm
trying to explain some news and have a
nice like little highlight animation.
Now, when I used Fable to do the same
prompt, it actually did even better. So,
here's some examples of that. This time
I use the redeploying fable one. And you
can see the highlight looks a little
more natural. And when it animates to
different highlight areas, it just feels
a little bit smoother, but it's still
the same process. It's still used code
behind the screen and used screenshots.
You can also do things like this where
it zooms in and points an arrow at a
specific piece of text just like this.
Or you can do it where it zooms to an
area and then highlights that area like
this. But you could do those sort of
like text B-roll animations for your
videos literally using Cloud Code. It
would probably work in Codeex as well,
but I tested it in Claude Code or I
guess Claude Co-work for this example.
You can also find that cheesy looking
corporate B-roll style video that you'd
find on stock video websites. If you
don't want to use a stock video website,
you can see my prompt here. Stock
footage of a man in a business suit
shaking hands with a woman in a business
suit while standing in a conference
room. And that's exactly what you get.
And here's another example of that exact
same prompt. I mean, it looks pretty
spot-on to what you would get out of one
of those B-roll websites. Here's one
where I have it with a stock B-roll
footage. A man sits on a pile of money
and scoops it from the ground and
excitedly tosses it in the air. Like,
come on. That's exactly what you'd find
on a B-roll website. Here's another
version of that same prompt. So, if you
need some decent looking B-roll, but
don't want to use a stock video site,
you want to dial it in for exactly what
you want, well, you can use Runway and
something like Seed Dance for that or,
you know, Leonardo and Clling or VO3.
Pretty much any of them these days will
make this style stock footage, probably
cuz there's a ton of it trained into the
training data already. Another thing you
can use AI tools for are text animations
and logo reveals. So the way I like to
do these is I actually like to do these
inside of codeex, but this also works
just as well in claude code and you
install a skill called remotion best
practices. Now if you haven't seen my
video about skills, definitely check
that video out. This is one of the
skills we kind of deep dive on, but you
install this skill inside of Codeex or
inside of Claude Code. To do that, you
open up codeex, go to plugins, go to
skills up here, search up remotion,
install reotion best practices, and you
can use this skill. So, I uploaded my
future tools logo here into codeex. And
I tagged Remotion best practices. So, I
just type slash and then type reotion
and then I'll select Remotion best
practices here. And then I would enter
my prompt next to that. There's an
explosion of particles and then the
particles reform to become the Future
Tools logo, which you know is the logo
that I uploaded with it. And here's that
animation that it created for me. All
the particles explode and then they form
directly into that Future Tools logo for
me. So that's something that you can use
like right at the intro of a video if
you want. Here's another version of the
particle logo reveal using my color
version of my logo. And here's what this
one looks like. You can see it's now
colorful but pretty much doing the same
thing. Here's another one I did where I
used the remote skill. Start from a
blank screen. Paint splatters all over
the screen in the colors of my avatar.
The paint drips and morphs into the
avatar image. And I uploaded my avatar.
And here's the video that that
generated. You can see all of the colors
splat all over the screen and then they
sort of rearrange and form into my
avatar. You can also use AI to create
lower thirds. Remotion does this really,
really well. You can also use the video
generators to do that, albeit it doesn't
always work quite as well. Here's some
examples of using seed dance where it
spells my name wrong and then says CEO
of Busybench where if you look at my
prompt here, it's supposed to create a
lower thirds saying my name correctly
and CEO of beauty bench. But we can see
it did create a sort of green screen
background here that if we were to
download this, pull it into Da Vinci
Resolve here, I can actually open this
in the Fusion editor here. I like to use
the delta key. So if I add the delta key
in here, come select my background color
as green by dragging this over right
here. Now if I watch my video, you can
see this animate onto the screen like
that. And then I can adjust the position
like this. Position it over here like
this. Maybe make it a little smaller.
And now I've got a little animation.
It's kind of a bummer that it didn't do
the text right because it actually looks
pretty good. Here's another example
that's even worse. CEO of Busty Bench,
but you get the idea. You can prompt it
to create a green screen lower third
graphic. Tell it what you want to say on
the lower third and it might create it.
Most likely you're going to have to
prompt it like four or five times before
it gets it right. Unless you're just
okay being the CEO of Busty Bench. Don't
look that up. Now, if I switch the model
over to VO3.1,
it actually does a much better job with
the text. So, you know, different models
are better for different things. here.
If I pull this one into Da Vinci
Resolve, there you go. You got a pretty
nice looking animated lower third that
is just better than what you're going to
get directly inside of something like Da
Vinci. Now, the other option to get this
kind of thing is to go back to Remotion.
And Remotion, it's going to dial in the
text perfectly every time cuz it's using
essentially code to make these videos,
but it's not going to look quite as epic
with the animations. So you can see I
used Remotion, gave it the exact same
prompt inside of Remotion, and well,
here's the version that Remotion made.
You can see not quite as flashy, but it
nailed the text and everything I asked
for. And it's got a perfect green screen
background. So adding our delta key on
that one, this one looks pretty perfect
as well. If you want to animate text
that comes in behind somebody, these
days it's not that hard to do it in
something like Da Vinci Resolve, but you
can ask Gemini to do it. Here's my
prompt for that. and it made a video
where the future tools text animates in
behind me instead of in front of me.
Maybe I want to do a fun little like
thought bubble. I can use a prompt like
this one right here. And you get a video
where I'm sitting here and now I'm
thinking everyone should really
subscribe after this one. So yeah, AI is
great for your logo reveals, animating
images onto the screen, putting text
behind you, putting thought bubbles,
adding lower thirds. You can do all of
that with AI. It's just sometimes it
might take you more than one prompt to
get it looking the way you want. But if
you really don't know your way around a
video editor like Da Vinci Resolve or
Adobe Premiere, this is a pretty easy
way to get what you're looking for
without needing to go and hire a
separate editor. Another thing that AI
is getting better and better at is doing
like these animated motion graphics.
Like the best way I can sort of describe
them is the type of things you might see
in like a Buzzfeed or Cleo Abrams or
Johnny Harris style video. Now, they're
not as good as if you were to hire
somebody and do them in After Effects
yourself, but you can get some fairly
decent style motion graphics. For
example, here's one that I did with
Remotion inside of Codeex where I
basically asked it to create like a mock
text message exchange. And here's what
it gave me. We can see it looks like an
iPhone. It says, "Have you subscribed to
Future Tools yet?" No. Why? Because it's
literally how people are keeping up with
AI news these days. Oh, okay. That's how
they're doing it. Just subbed. Thanks.
like this exact text exchange would
probably work decent as an ad to get
people to go subscribe to the
newsletter. If you're telling a story
about a text exchange that you had on a
video, well, you can use this kind of
animation for that. If you want to see
the exact prompt I used, feel free to
pause and and take a peek, but uh it
works well for that kind of thing.
Another example is if you're trying to
explain a complex topic and you need a
sort of visual to go along with that
explanation. Like when I gave it this
prompt here to explain what SVG images
are and how SVG actually uses code, it
generated this video here showing that
the code is what turns into the image.
Or this one here where explaining how my
Gary Buucy leaderboard works. I mean,
it's a pretty decent little animation,
especially when you know the context of
the rest of my video. Now, another good
way to get some of these motion graphic
type things is to use Notebook LM. You
can actually feed it a bunch of
documents on the topic that you're
trying to explain. And inside of
Notebook LM, you can do things like
create audio podcasts and slide decks
and things like that. But there's also
this video overview feature here where
you can have it create cinematic
overviews or explainers or shorts. And
in this case with this sort of birds
aren't real one that I've played with in
the past. You can see that it made this
animation for me that looks pretty good.
Now I can scroll through this and
there's parts of this animation that
would make for a great video on this
topic. Like here's a funny chart that it
made about drones going up as the amount
of birds are going down. Here's one that
explains that the birds get their energy
by sitting on telephone wires. And
here's like a really cool animation of a
guy holding a bird. Like if I was making
a legit video about this topic, the
animations that Notebook LM creates
around the sources that you feed it are
actually really good animations that are
very usable for B-roll. Jumping back to
codecs here, another really useful
animation style, especially if you're
doing an explainer video or like a mini
doc or something like that, you might
want to show some graphs. Here's one
that shows Nvidia's stock chart growth.
That again, another really solid
animation that can be used if you're
making a video about Nvidia's growth.
Now, one thing that's been sort of hit
or miss and I haven't really got it to
work that well is I want to get this
visual of like a plane going from one
city to another. That might work really
well for like a travel video except all
of the video generators are kind of
pretty bad at it. So, here's what Seed
Dance does. You can see that here's my
plane starting in the state of Slinkke
and it flies over E over the state of
NRA and Durk and Brau and lands
somewhere near Navulk when I told it to
go from San Diego to New York. And yeah,
you you could just it's it's not great.
Here's my second attempt. Maybe a little
bit better. Like San Diego is not here.
It's way down here. But you can see this
video. It sort of flies over the state,
sort of weaves up, and then overshoots
New York a little bit. [laughter]
I mean, better than the last one, but
still not super accurate. I tried to get
the same thing to work over in Gemini
using the Omni model, and we got a
similar issue. It did start in San
Diego. It flies across, and it does seem
to land kind of where New York is. My
main complaint about this one is like
halfway through the video you could see
it sort of like fades out and sort of
goes backwards, right? So right here
we're over like Nebraska area, right
here we're over Illinois, but then all
of a sudden we're back over Arizona
again. So it sort of has this weird blip
in the middle of it. But the starting
and ending are a lot more accurate than
the other options I got. But the best
one does seem to be using Remotion in
Codeex. But again, it's just not quite
as cool looking. Here's what that one
generated. You can see it's just an
arrow and it flies from San Diego to New
York. It kind of takes this weird upper
arc instead of just kind of shooting it
across in a straight line. But it's
definitely the most sort of accurate
city to city of them all. So depending
on what you're going for, try some
options. If you're going to use one of
the AI models and not, you know, a code
model like Remotion, you might have to
prompt it a few times before you get
what you're looking for. Okay, there's
one last video type I want to talk about
because it was another little trick that
I used in one of my videos and a lot of
people asked me how'd you do that. So,
in this video that I released back on
May 8th, I sort of broke down this text
exchange between Sam Alman and Mera
Marotti and here's what that looked
like. Sam asked, can you indicate
directionally good or bad? Satya and
others are anxious. Directionally very
bad. Okay. Can you wrap up soon? Lots of
pressure from Microsoft for an update.
Sam, this is very bad. And again, I got
a lot of questions about how did you
actually do that? So, what I did was I
read the text messages out loud. I just
used Da Vinci Resolve's audio recorder
and just recorded myself reading all of
the text exchange. Inside of Runway,
they have this feature called character
script to video. And if I select this
feature, I can upload an image. So, I
uploaded this image of Sam Alman that I
found. I think it was actually an AI
generated image of Sam cuz it doesn't
really look totally like him. And then
under character script, you have the
option to type a script or upload audio.
So I uploaded the audio of me speaking
out this exchange. I did the same thing
for Mirror Morati. The output looked
like this. It was an entire video of one
person saying both the lines. Sam asked,
"Can you indicate directionally good or
bad? Satya and others are anxious." Mera
said, "Directionally very bad." So both
videos looked just like that with the
entire dialogue of both. I pull them
into Da Vinci, my editing software, and
I just edit them having the conversation
back and forth. I find little stuff like
that keeps people engaged in the videos
longer. If it was just a video of me
just rambling and talking about the news
for the entire video, people tend to
check out and tune out. So, when I do
stuff like this, it tends to get people
to stick around and watch videos longer
because they're always waiting to see
like what little fun Easter eggs or toys
or tools am I going to throw in to make
the video more entertaining, more
interesting to watch. And those are some
of the ways that I use AI to create
visual effects inside of my videos to
keep them exciting and intriguing and
fun and entertaining. And also, let's be
honest, I'm doing it to entertain
myself. Like I have a lot of fun
figuring out what tools to use and how
to get these different things to make
the animations that I'm looking to get
them to make. And it's a really
enjoyable process. Now, I know this
video probably wasn't for everybody.
There's a lot of people that come to my
channel and tune in for the AI news that
I put out every Friday. And well, this
wasn't that. But there's also a lot of
people that probably want to learn how
to do some really fun little things with
AI video tools to improve their videos.
That's who I made this video for. I
mean, you could use these AI video tools
to create slop that no one wants to see,
or you could use them to add little
touches of spice to your own videos and
really grab that attention. Me
personally, I still prefer to make 95%
human videos and use AI about 5% of the
time. And again, it's more just to
inject a little bit of fun and silliness
into the video and not to like be the
video itself. If I'm being honest, I'm
not really looking forward to a world
where everything we see online has very
little human involvement. Like I'm
already getting on a lot of these
platforms and noticing that I'm having a
harder and harder time telling what's
actually AI and what's not anymore. And
I don't really like that. So when I use
AI, I almost like purposely show off
that it is AI. So nobody's wondering if
this was done with AI or not. But that's
just sort of the style that I like
doing. But that's what I got for you
today. Hopefully you found this helpful.
Hopefully you learned something. If you
like videos like this and you actually
want to learn practical, actually useful
ways to leverage these AI tools that are
coming out. I try to make at least one
video a week where I'm showing you how
to use these tools and how to implement
them in your business or your life. And
I'm also making at least one video a
week where I break down all of the AI
news that I think you need to know. I
drink from the fire hose all week. I get
sort of overwhelmed by all the AI news
so that you don't have to. And then
every Friday, I break down just the most
important AI news that I think the most
people would want to know. If those are
the types of videos that you think you'd
enjoy more of, consider liking this
video and subscribing to this channel.
I'll make sure that kind of stuff shows
up in your feed and that you'll always
feel looped in. Thanks so much for
hanging out, nerding out with me on this
one. It's always fun when I get to make
videos like this, so hopefully you
enjoyed it. If you want to see more of
them, let me know in the comments.
Thanks again. Hopefully I'll see you in
the next one. Bye-bye.